AKHIL MATHEW

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

Solutions-focused and goal-oriented software engineer with four years of experience in implementing advanced technology and business solutions. Demonstrates strong analytical and problem-solving skills and the ability to follow through with projects from inception to completion.

Experience

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

TechNeurons, Cochin | 2021 - Present Handles and leads all major developments in the project. Supervise all the activities of development team.

ASSOCIATE PROGRAMMER

TechNeurons, Cochin | 2018 - 2021 Collaborated with team members in understanding the project and during development.

Education

COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING

Holy Kings College of Engineering & Technology Muvattupuzh a | 2013 - 2017

HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION

G.H.S.S Pampakuda, Muvattupuzha | 2011 - 2013

Personal Projects

Portfolio Website

Personal website created with HTML, CSS and JS

Chat App

Simple group chat web app made with React, Node and Socket

Meeting Room Booking Application

Application for booking meeting rooms in an organization made with Node express, EJS and Mongo DB

Personal information

Name

Akhil Mathew

Birthdate

26/07/1996

Gender

Male

Residence

Cochin

Nationality

India

Skills

Programming Technologies

VB .NET

JS/Jquery

Node JS

Python

C#

React



DataBase

SQL Server Mongo DB

SOI ite

Frameworks

WPF

NFT

Pyqt



Personality Traits

- Problem Solving & Analytical Skills
- Dedicated
- Decision Making

Contact

- ☆ Cochin, Kerala
- 9562 458 658
- ≥ akhilmathew4045@gmail.com
- in akhil-mathew-073b28238
- akhilMa89152309